{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Cāntīng" ,
      "answer": "餐厅"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zài (In)",
      "answer": "在"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nǎr" ,
      "answer": "哪儿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qǐngwèn",
      "answer": "请问"
    },
    {
      "question": "wèn",
      "answer": "问"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhè",
      "answer": "这"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sùshè",
      "answer": "宿舍"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nǚ",
      "answer": "女"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuéshēng",
      "answer": "学生"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jìn",
      "answer": "进"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zuò",
      "answer": "坐"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xièxiè",
      "answer": "谢谢"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duìbùqǐ",
      "answer": "对不起"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wǒ",
      "answer": "我"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhīdào",
      "answer": "知道"
    },
    {
      "question": "Méiguānxì",
      "answer": "没关系"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hǎo",
      "answer": "好"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zàijiàn",
      "answer": "再见"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zài (Again)",
      "answer": "再"
    }
  ]
}
